Mahadi Hasan



mahadi.dev.pm@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/mahadidev



01408094722



https://mahadidev.vercel.app

Summary

I am a Full Stack Web developer with more than 3 years of experience in this field. I have been working in a freelance marketplace. I started my coding/career when I was 14. Now I am 18. I am a young professional passionate about web development and design. My mission is to help you grow your business

Experience



Senior Web Developer

Upwork

Jan 2023 - Present (1 month)

I recently started working on Upwork on 1st Jan 2023.

Freelance Web Developer

Freelancer.com

Jan 2020 - Present (3 years 1 month)

I have been working on this freelance marketplace since 2020. I started my career when I was 14. I got my first account suspended to use my fake identity. I used fake identity for my age.

Web Developer

Fiverr

Apr 2020 - Dec 2022 (2 years 9 months)

I was working as a Web Developer on fiverr.com I stopped working in this site 12 months ago.

Education



Dighalia Ideal Secondary School

High School Diploma, Business/Commerce, General

Jan 2017 - Apr 2033

I have been studying at Business line but I feel good while I do coding.

Skills

Adobe Premiere Pro · Adobe Photoshop · jQuery · Tailwind CSS · Cascading Style Sheets (CSS) · HTML5 • MySQL • TypeScript • PHP • JavaScript